

Nasiru Hammed A.

Web Developer | Architect







I am a positive, enthusiastic and competent Web
Developer who, over some months, has built up a
diverse range of skills, qualities and attributes that
guarantee I will perform highly in this role. I have
experience working both alone and as part of a
team on often time-sensitive, challenging web
development projects that require outstanding
creative and technical capabilities and the ability to
ensure all work is optimized across a wide range of
platforms.

NASIRU HAMMED

Web developer | Architect

nasaces360@gmail.com

09082716040, 09082716040

EDUCATION & TRAINING -

Tech Accent Creatives

Full stack web development

Bells University of Technology

Ogun, Nigeria Bsc. Architecture, 2021

lagos, Nigeria

Federal polytechnic Auchi

Edo, Nigeria HND. Architecture, 2017

EXPERIENCE -

Web developement intern

Tech Accent Creatives

July 29 - till date

Participate in conception, design, development, implementation and deployment of web-based user interface systems, Create cross-browser, fully functional web pages using HTML and CSS while strictly adhering to accessibility and W3C web standards, Develop web applications using JavaScript, HTML and CSS.

Architect Ry Projects

Jan 2018 - Dec 2022

Preparation or architectural drawings, working drawings and presentation drawings, Assisted in initial project research and outlining project schedule and task, Supervised construction site, Visualizing 3D renders of proposed spaces.

Intern DIC projects

Jan 2016 - Dec 2017

Preparation and coordination of the details of architectural projects which includes building specification and dimensions, Assisted in initial project research and outlining project schedule and task, Supervised construction site, Visualizing 3D renders of proposed spaces

Intern Linesmith design associate

Jan 2015 - Dec 2016

Preparation of complete working and presentation drawing in AutoCAD and Revit Architecture, Completion of construction documents, Assisted in the reviews of project proposal, Site supervision.

Intern Team design Africa

Jan 2015 - Dec 2016

Preparation of complete working and presentation drawing in AutoCAD and Revit Architecture, Completion of construction documents, Assisted in the reviews of project proposal, Site supervision.

SKILL -

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React js

Testing/

debugging

Version control/Git

Node js

Responsive design

Express js

jQuery

MongoDB

EmailContactLocationnasaces360@gmail.com+234-9082-7160-40Lagos, Nigeria